http://www.privatelessons.com/privacy-policy

Events
Join Now!
Find a Music Teacher
Instrument or Music Genre *
US/Canada City or Zip/Postal Code
Privacy Policy
The following is PrivateLessons.com privacy policy.
Information Collection
We collect personal information when you voluntarily sign up for an account. We do not sell or rent personal information.
We do not collect or keep your Credit Card information on PrivateLessons.com site. Payments are processed over secure servers of our authorized processors: PayPal, Inc. & BankCardUSA.
We use your personal email to communicate with you. We have your consent to communicate with you by email as many times as necessary.
We use external mapping service, Google Maps, to show your general geographic location based on street address data you provide in your profile. We do not publish your personal address on PrivateLessons.com pages, however that information displays on pages of mapping service site. We recommend that you show INTERSECTION vs. ACTUAL ADDRESS.Example: North & South Streets, Anytown, USA 12345
The public can contact you via private messaging. Messages are found inside your account.
We reserve the right to reject and/or discontinue any account, for any reason.
Content
You own your content. You are responsible for keeping back-up records of that information.
Your profile displays on our public pages. You are responsible for maintaining complete and high quality content.
Do not publish copyrighted material.
To promote PrivateLessons.com, for the common good of the service, we reserve the right to use your photos, videos, still frame images, and content in any advertising and social media re-posts.
Security
Your account is password-protected. We encourage you to change your password periodically.
This system expires private data page views, providing added security when you use public computer terminals.
Cookies
Portions of the Service require cookies.
Editing, Renewing, Account Removal Requests
You can edit your account information at any time.
To renew your inactive PrivateLessons.com account, login to your account and follow renewal instructions.
Account Removal Request - Login to your account and submit a request for removal.
Privacy Policy Amendments
We may periodically amend this policy and without notice. Please check this page often.
Instruments
Accordion
Acoustic Guitar
Banjo
Bass
Bass Guitar
Bassoon
Bongo
TV Scoring
Albany, NY Music LessonsAlbuquerque, NM Music LessonsAnaheim, CA Music LessonsAnchorage, AK Music LessonsAtlanta, GA Music LessonsAustin, TX Music LessonsBaltimore, MD Music LessonsBaton Rouge, LA Music LessonsBellevue, WA Music LessonsBirmingham, AL Music LessonsBloomington, IN Music LessonsBoca Raton, FL Music LessonsBoston, MA Music LessonsBoulder, CO Music LessonsBrooklyn, NY Music LessonsBuffalo, NY Music LessonsCalgary, Canada Music LessonsCharlotte, NC Music LessonsChesapeake, VA Music LessonsChicago, IL Music LessonsCincinnati, OH Music LessonsCleveland, OH Music LessonsColumbus, OH Music LessonsDallas, TX Music LessonsDenver, CO Music LessonsDetroit, MI Music LessonsDurham, NC Music LessonsEdmonton, Canada Music LessonsFort Lauderdale, FL Music LessonsFort Worth, TX Music LessonsFresno, CA Music LessonsGrand Rapids, MI Music LessonsGreensboro, NC Music LessonsGreenville, SC Music LessonsHarrisburg, PA Music LessonsHartford, CT Music LessonsHonolulu, HI Music LessonsHouston, TX Music LessonsHuntsville, AL Music LessonsIndianapolis, IN Music LessonsJacksonville, FL Music LessonsJersey City, NJ Music LessonsKansas City, MO Music LessonsLas Vegas, NV Music LessonsLexington, KY Music LessonsLincoln, NE Music LessonsLittle Rock, AR Music LessonsLong Beach, CA Music LessonsLong Island City, NY Music LessonsLos Angeles, CA Music LessonsMadison, WI Music LessonsManchester, NH Music LessonsMemphis, TN Music LessonsMiami, FL Music LessonsMilwaukee, WI Music LessonsMinneapolis, MN Music LessonsMontreal, Canada Music LessonsNashua, NH Music LessonsNashville, TN Music LessonsNew Haven, CT Music LessonsNew Orleans, LA Music LessonsNew York, NY Music LessonsNorfolk, VA Music LessonsOakland, CA Music LessonsOklahoma City, OK Music LessonsOrlando, FL Music LessonsOttawa, Canada Music LessonsPalm Beach, FL Music LessonsPhiladelphia, PA Music LessonsPhoenix, AZ Music LessonsPittsburgh, PA Music LessonsPlano, TX Music LessonsPortland, OR Music LessonsProvidence, RI Music LessonsRaleigh, NC Music LessonsRichmond, VA Music LessonsRiverside, CA Music LessonsRoanoke, VA Music LessonsRochester, NY Music LessonsSacramento, CA Music LessonsSalt Lake City, UT Music LessonsSan Antonio, TX Music LessonsSan Bernardino, CA Music LessonsSan Diego, CA Music LessonsSan Francisco, CA Music LessonsSan Jose, CA Music LessonsSanta Ana, CA Music LessonsSarasota, FL Music LessonsScottsdale, AZ Music LessonsSeattle, WA Music LessonsSpringfield, MA Music LessonsSt. Louis, MO Music LessonsSt. Paul, MN Music LessonsSyracuse, NY Music LessonsTacoma, WA Music LessonsTallahassee, FL Music LessonsTampa, FL Music LessonsToronto, Canada Music LessonsTucson, AZ Music LessonsTulsa, OK Music LessonsVancouver, Canada Music LessonsVirginia Beach, VA Music LessonsWashington, DC Music LessonsWestchester, NY Music LessonsWilmington, DE Music LessonsWinston-Salem, NC Music Lessons
Home
Articles
Events
Join Now!
Membership
About
Contact
Log In
Founded in 1996, PrivateLessons.com is a professional network of independent music teachers. © Copyright 2020. All Rights Reserved. Terms of Use • Privacy Policy
